opencsgo.com 2018-04-19

# Privacy Policy - OpenCSGO.com

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which opencsgo.dev collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the opencsgo.dev website ("Site") in accordance with United Kingdom legislation.

###### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site by logging in via Steam or other service, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

###### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the country you connect from, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

###### Disclosure of personal information to third parties

As a policy all authorities will not disclose any personal information to anyone other than those employees or third parties that need access to your data to provide you with a service.

We may be required by law or legal process to disclose your personal information to authorities such as the VAT department, HMRC, and other similar authorities.

###### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. For example, we use a cookie to remember your currency preference. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

###### How we use collected information

opencsgo.dev may collect and use Users personal (Steam) information for the following purposes:

  * To run and operate our Site 
  * We may need your information display content on the Site correctly. 
  * To personalize user experience 
  * We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. 
  * To improve our Site 
  * We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services. 
  * To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature 
  * To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them. 

###### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

###### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share push database and generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

###### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licencors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

###### Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

###### Compliance with children's online privacy protection act

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

###### Changes to this privacy policy

opencsgo.dev has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

###### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

###### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at [support@opencsgo.dev](mailto:support@opencsgo.dev)

Revised January 30, 2017
